Abdullah ElGamal

FULL STACK WFB DEVELOPER

SKILLS

Back-end

Node.is Php Laravel

Front-end

HTML CSS **JavaScript Typescript** Vue Angular Bootstrab Jquery

Databases

MYSOL **SOL SERVER** Oracle

Desktop Application

C# Java

Android Application

Java Kotlin OS

Windows Linux

Graphics

Photoshop

CONTACT

Contact

- menoufia menouf
- **** 01204299614
- ≥ ggamals7744@yahoo.com

Link

- nero-soft.firebaseapp.com
- github.com/Nerosoft
- youtube.com/coursesonline

SUMMARY

I have 5 + years experience of software development. I like working on the edge when it comes to user experience design, and love the challenge of bringing new ideas to life. I am passionate about what I do and look forward to assignments that enable me to add value and expand my horizons. I can stick to deadlines, work under-pressure and work with minimal or no supervision.

I have worked in application web and android development

EXPERIENCE

2020 - Present **FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPER** self study, internet courses Firebase, Node js, Angular 2018 - 2019 **Android developer** self study, internet courses Java, Kotlin, Firebase 2017 - 2018 Web programing self study, internet courses Node.js, Php, Laravel, 2016 - 2017 **Web Designer** self study, internet courses Html, css, Java Script, Angular, Vue 2015 - 2016 **Desktop Application** self study, internet courses C#, Sal Server, Mysal

EDUCATION

2020 - Present **Diploma/IS- DBMS** computer science, fayoum university Database is an organized collection of data, generally stored and accessed electronically from a computer system. Where databases are more complex they are often developed using formal design and modeling techniques.

2015 - 2018

Bachelor's degree/MIS

computer science, eg academy in tanta A management information system (MIS) is an information system used for decision-making, and for the coordination, control, analysis, and visualization of information in an organization

PROJECTS

Smart Home Arabic

make your house a smart home. Arduino, Node js, Angular, Java Android

PORTFOLIOS

nero-soft.firebaseapp.com/